A Guide to the Foundation for Child Development (Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City) records FA405
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, 1904-1915, 1919-1920, 1931-1933; bulk
  - Administration - Board of Directors Meetings, 1904-1915, 1919-1920, 1931-1933; bulk
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, October 15, 1919 (Reel 1, Frame 134)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, December 11, 1919 (Reel 1, Frame 135)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, January 8, 1920 (Reel 1, Frame 136)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, February 26, 1920 (Reel 1, Frame 137)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, October 8, 1931 (Reel 1, Frame 138)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, November 2, 1931 (Reel 1, Frame 139)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, December 7, 1931 (Reel 1, Frame 140)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, January 4, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 141)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, February 1, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 142)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, March 7, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 143)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, April 4, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 144)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, October 10, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 145)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, November 14, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 146)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, December 4, 1932 (Reel 1, Frame 147)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, January 9, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 148)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, February 6, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 149)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, March 6, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 150)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, April 3, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 151)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, May 1, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 152)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes - No Meeting, October 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 153)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, November 6, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 154)
    - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, December 4, 1933 (Reel 1, Frame 155)